=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 21=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 21 =
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
This is Master Bo Yi.
هذا هو المعلم بو يي.
Hello, master.
مرحبا سيد.
I know the purpose
أعرف الغرض
of your visit.
من زيارتك.
I can break
يمكنني كسر
the spell of the bracelet,
تعويذة السوار
but
لكن
can you bear the consequences of it?
هل تستطيع تحمل عواقب ذلك؟
Tell us, master.
أخبرنا يا سيد.
We can handle it.
نتمكن من التعامل معها.
He came from a painting
لقد جاء من لوحة
and you are a person of the present.
وأنت شخص الحاضر.
If I break the connection
إذا قطعت الاتصال
between you and the bracelet,
بينك وبين السوار
you will each return to your place
سوف يعود كل منك إلى مكانك
and he will return to the portrait.
وسيعود إلى الصورة.
That won't do.
هذا لن ينفع.
He has to continue his medical studies
عليه أن يواصل دراسته الطبية
and work for the clinic.
والعمل في العيادة.
Tang Qinjian
تانغ كينجيان
was the head of the Imperial Medical Office
كان رئيس المكتب الطبي الإمبراطوري
during the Kaiyuan period of the Tang dynasty
خلال فترة Kaiyuan من أسرة Tang
and was hailed by the people
وأشاد به الشعب
as Divine Physician.
كطبيب إلهي.
Does he still need to study medicine?
هل مازال بحاجة لدراسة الطب؟
So his name is Tang Qinjian.
إذن اسمه تانغ كينجين.
I don't care who he is,
لا يهمني من هو
but he can't leave without my permission.
لكنه لا يستطيع المغادرة بدون إذني.
Master.
يتقن.
Can you think of any other way?
هل يمكنك التفكير بأي طريقة أخرى؟
There is indeed another way
هناك بالفعل طريقة أخرى
to break the spell.
لكسر التعويذة.
Give me the jade pendant.
أعطني قلادة اليشم.
This jade pendant
هذا قلادة اليشم
will temporarily help you to stay,
سيساعدك مؤقتًا على البقاء ،
but only for 30 days.
ولكن لمدة 30 يومًا فقط.
You can be resurrected
يمكنك القيام
only if you find
فقط إذا وجدت
a soulmate of the opposite gender
توأم الروح من الجنس الآخر
within 30 days.
خلال 30 يوما.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
your soul will be shattered
روحك ستتحطم
and you will cease to exist.
وسوف تختفي من الوجود.
No way, master.
مستحيل يا سيد.
Thirty days is too short.
ثلاثون يومًا قصيرة جدًا.
Can he find one as we connect?
هل يمكنه العثور على واحد ونحن نتواصل؟
Physician Tang.
الطبيب تانغ.
Please
لو سمحت
come closer.
اقترب.
The bracelet and the jade pendant
السوار وقلادة اليشم
were meant to be
كان من المفترض أن يكون
two pieces of a single stone.
قطعتين من حجر واحد.
You would have been perfect for each other,
كنتم ستكونون مثاليين لبعضكم البعض ،
but
لكن
your life span is over.
انتهت فترة حياتك.
You two
أنت أيضا
are not just linked by marriage,
ليست مرتبطة فقط بالزواج ،
but also tied by a lifeline.
ولكن أيضًا مقيدة بشريان الحياة.
When tied together,
عندما نرتبط ببعضها البعض ،
her life will be shortened
سوف تقصر حياتها
and her body will weaken rapidly.
وسيضعف جسدها بسرعة.
The only way
الطريقة الوحيدة
to stop this is
لوقف هذا
to untie the string.
لفك الخيط.
Her fainting
إغماءها
just now
الآن
was one of the signs.
كانت إحدى العلامات.
Break the spell.
كسر التعويذة.
Are you sure about this?
هل أنت متأكدة من هذا؟
I disagree.
أنا أعترض.
I have made up my mind.
أنت اتخذت قراري.
Master.
يتقن.
Please begin.
من فضلك ابدأ.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض